

# **EVANS WAKABA GICHUNJI**

(a) info@evanswakaba.me.ke

)+971 55 8688091

# ⊘ONLINE PROFILE evanswakaba.me.ke

#### SKILLS

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Communication

Leadership

Interpersonal

#### CODING SKILLS

html & css

Java Script

Back-end (nodeJS & SQL)

#### SOFTWARE/TECHNOLOGY SKILLS

Photoshop

Joomla

GIT

https://github.com/divineevans

NATIONALITY: Kenyan VISA TYPE: Visit

## CAREER OBJECTIVE

To utilize my knowledge, skills and experience as a Front-Web Developer in providing quality and excellent services in a position where my qualities as a fast learner, a motivator, a passionate leader and a dedicated team player can be put to maximum use.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Jan 2016 to date, Freelancing

### Web Developer and Graphics Design

- -Designed an ecommerce website for a furniture company which significantly increased customer interaction and convenience
- -Developed a hotel's website and increased the hotel's online presence by 60% and also generated presence in social media.
- -Did branding for over 20 SME's which boosted their sales opportunites significantly.

#### Apr 2013 - Apr 2014, Light Academy

#### IT instructor/Teacher

- Teaching ICT from year 7 to year 11 (IGCSE curriculum)
- Maintaining school LAN and website
- Computer hardware and software maintenance

# VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

#### May 2014 - Jan 2019. LoveWorld Inc

- Spearheaded a team of 10 in a social media campaign. Our creative content and targetted hash tags led to user engagement of over 100%.
- Designed an online registration form for a youth conference. and increased data collection and retainership by 30%.
- Headed the IT department. Oversaw social media content creation, organised online meetings, initiated IT trainings and inspired several of them to monetize their skills.

## **EDUCATION**

2006 - 2011 (Kenyatta University) BSC

(Telecommunications & Information Technology)

- Followed my passion for computers and web development.
- Among the few choosen for special IT training by Knowledge For Life organisation.
- -Participated in Telecommunications seminars & clubs.